If they told you black people could not serve on juries, we'd be marching on Washington.
Yes.
OK, but we can serve on juries.
In fact, the Supreme Court said it in 1886.
It was a big deal.
Strouder versus West Virginia.
Maybe it was 1883.
The point is that we are not supposed to be kept from serving, serving on juries.
And yet when we have the opportunity to do so, we opt out.
So we've got jury service.
We've got voting, which we're either not doing.
Well, why do you think we're doing that, though?
Why do you think we're opting out?
Why do you think we're turning our head, checking out instead of being involved in these spaces?
Well, I do think part of it is the reason why I'm on this show, Amanda, is that I think we have not been sufficiently educated about these things as conduits to power.
Right. So if I tell you about the railroad commissioner, I tell you about the probate judge or I tell you about, you know, any of these offices and how they're empowered to affect your life.
I think that people are unaware.